Guide to the Mick Moloney Irish-American Music and Popular Culture Papers AIA.031.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: Individuals, 1879-2010; 5 boxes
  - Bradshaw, Harry, 1982-1991 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Brady, Paul, 1977-1991 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Bretholz, Myron, 1978-1980 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Britton, Tim, 1977, 1979 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Burke, Joe "Accordion", c. 1981 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Burke, Kevin, c. 1978, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Butler, Jean, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Carnloch, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Cahill, Eddie, 1980-1982 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Carawan, Deborah Canady, 1989, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Carroll, Liz, c. 1976-1994 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Carton, Mickey, undated, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Cassidy, Peter, 1998, 2000 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Correspondence, 1944-1963 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Correspondence, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: General, 1933-c.1977 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Irish Musicians' Association of America, 1940s-1950s (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Irish Musicians' Union of Pennsylvania, 1943, 1947 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Irish Musicians' Union of Pennsylvania: Ledgerbooks, 1938-1948 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Pamphlets, 1952 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Programs, 1933-1944 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Programs, 1946 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: 1947-1963 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Radio Advertisements and Scripts (Folder 1), undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Radio Advertisements and Scripts (Folder 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: Radio Advertising Receipts, 1947-1948 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Caulfield, Tommy: John J. O'Kane Poems and Memoir, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Celtic Thunder, 1981 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Celtic Thunder, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Cherish the Ladies: Clippings, 1985-1998 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Cherish the Ladies: General (Folder 1), 1985-1988 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Cherish the Ladies: General (Folder 2), 1988-2000 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Cherish the Ladies: Posters (Oversized), 1986, undated (Flat-file-folder 3)
  - Cherish the Ladies: Promotional Materials, undated, 1994-2000 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Chieftains, 1978-1998 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Clancy Brothers: General, 1969-1999 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Clancy Brothers: Promotional Materials, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Clark, Dennis: Correspondence, 1974-1992 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Clark, Dennis: General, 1972-1993 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Clark, Dennis: Research Materials, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Clark, Dennis: Writings (Folder 1), 1980s (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Clark, Dennis: Writings (Folder 2), undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Coen, Fr. Charlie, 1979-1980 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Coen, Jack, 1979-1993 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Cohan, George M., 1990 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Cole, Lori, 1980-1981 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Coleman, Michael, 1977-1992 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Collins, Gus, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Connolly, Seamus, undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Conway, Brian, circa 1977, 1999 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Creagh, Marie Annick, circa 1991 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Crehan Family, undated (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Cronin, Paddy, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Crowley, Jimmy, undated, 1990s (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Cudahy, Dorothy Hayden, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - DeDanaan: Correspondence (Folder 1), 1978 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - DeDanaan: Correspondence (Folder 2), 1978-1979 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - DeDanaan: General, circa 1978 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Dennehy, Dennis, undated (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Devvane, Joe, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Doherty, Joe: Clippings, 1989-1992 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Doherty, Joe: Concert and Correspondence, 1989-1990 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Doherty, Tom, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Dolan, Felix, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Donnelly, Bob, 1997-2000 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Dunn, Captain Michael J., 1994 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Egan, Seamus (Folder 1), 1987-1992 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Egan, Seamus (Folder 2), 1992-1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Egan, Siobhan, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Ennis, Seamus, undated (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Fair, Darcy, 1991 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Faulkner, John, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Fentiman, Sharon, 1998 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Fidlusion, undated (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Flanagan, Mike, undated (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - Flatley, Michael, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - Foude, Declan, undated (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Foy, Barry: Field Guide to the Irish Music Session, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Friedman, Emily, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 36)
  - Gans, Jamie, undated (Box 16, Folder 37)
  - General: A-C, 1990-1997 (Box 16, Folder 38)
  - General: D-H, 1962-2000 (Box 16, Folder 39)
  - General: I-M, circa 1980-2000 (Box 16, Folder 40)
  - General: N-R, 1982-2000 (Box 16, Folder 41)
  - General: S-W, 1992-1999 (Box 16, Folder 42)
  - Gershen, Paulette, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 43)
  - Glassie, Henry, undated (Box 16, Folder 44)
  - Glassie, Henry (Oversized), undated (Box Shared Tamiment 080, Folder 11)
  - Golden, Donny, 1994-1996 (Box 16, Folder 45)
  - Goldstein, Kenny, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 46)
  - Gramarye, 1993 (Box 16, Folder 47)
  - Green Fields of America (Folder 1), 1979-1995 (Box 16, Folder 48)
  - Green Fields of America (Folder 2), undated (Box 16, Folder 49)
  - Green Fields of America (Folder 3), undated (Box 16, Folder 50)
  - Green Fields of America: Television Specials, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 51)
  - Green Fields of America: Tour, 1984 (Box 16, Folder 52)
  - Green Fields of America: Tour, 1989 (Box 16, Folder 53)
  - Green Crass Cloggers, undated (Box 16, Folder 54)
  - Harrigan and Hart, undated, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 55)
  - Harte, Frank: Correspondence, 1983-1984 (Box 16, Folder 56)
  - Hawes, Bess, undated (Box 16, Folder 57)
  - Hayden, James, undated (Box 16, Folder 58)
  - Healy, Shay, 1980 (Box 16, Folder 59)
  - Heaney, Joe: General, 1979-1996 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Heaney, Joe: General, undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Heaney, Joe: Transcripts, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Heron, Brian, circa 1980 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Herrmann, Lani, 1976-1978 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Hokkaneu, Niles, undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Irish Tradition, undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Irvine, Andy, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Ivers, Eileen, 1978-1996 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Johnstons, circa 1968 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Johnstons, 1989-1992 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Johnstons: Bookings and Correspondence (Folder 1), 1968 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Johnstons: Bookings and Correspondence (Folder 2), 1968-1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Johnstons: Poster (Oversized), undated (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Jordan, Kieran, 1992-1994 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Judkins, Charles, undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Keane, James, undated (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Keane, James "House", 1976 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Keane, Jerry, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Keenan, Paddy, undated (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Kelly, Gene: General, 1976-1979 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Kelly, Gene: Transcript, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Kelly, Walter, circa 1917 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Lamond, Mary Jane, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Larsen, Grey, 1986, 1998 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Liddy, James, 1980 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - MacMathuna, Ciaran, undated (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - MacConnell, Cormac (Folder 1), 1988-1998 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - MacConnell, Cormac (Folder 2), 1988-1998 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - MacMahon, Tony, 1972-1984 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Madden, Joanie, 1991-1995 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Magee, Colin, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Maids of Erin, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - McBee, Hamper, circa 1986 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - McCaffrey, Tom, undated (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - McCann, Jim, undated (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - McCormack, John, 1972-1992 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - McCourt, Frank, undated (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - McCourt, Malachy, undated (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - McCullough, L.E., 1975-1981 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - McDonough, Tim (Folder 1), undated (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - McDonough, Tim (Folder 2), undated (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - McEchron, Mary, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - McGann, Andy, 1981, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - McGettigan, John, 1937-1997 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - McGlynn, Sean, 1983, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - McGovern, Betsy, 1991-1992 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - McGrath, John, undated (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - McGreevy, Johnny and Joe Shannon, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - McGuire, P.J., 1946 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - McNamara's Band, 1997 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - McNulty, Eileen, 1982, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - McNulty Family, undated (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Miller, Kerby: Immigrant Letters (Folder 1), 1919-1946 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Miller, Kerby: Immigrant Letters (Folder 2), 1919-1946 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Miller, Kerby: Immigrant Letters (Folder 3), 1919-1946 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Miller, Kerby: Immigrant Letters (Folder 4), 1919-1946 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Miller, Kerby: Immigrant Letters (Folder 5), 1919-1946 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Mollys, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles About (Folder 1), circa 1970-1980 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles About (Folder 2), 1981-1986 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles About (Folder 3), 1987-1990 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles About (Folder 4), 1991-1992 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles About (Folder 5), 1993-2010 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles By (Folder 1), 1975-1991 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Moloney, Mick: Articles By (Folder 2), undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Moloney, Mick: Awards, Testimonials and Diplomas (Oversized), 1984-2001 (Box Shared Tamiment 142, Folder 2)
  - Moloney, Mick: Awards, Testimonials and Diplomas (Oversized), Jul, 1996 (Flat-file-folder 5)
  - Moloney, Mick: General, circa 1970-circa 2010 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Moloney, Mick: Order Forms, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Moloney, Mick: Press (Folder 1), 1973-1992 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Moloney, Mick: Press (Folder 2), 1992-1995 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Moloney, Mick: Press (Folder 3), 1995-2001, undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Moloney, Mick: Press Kit Materials, 1973-1998, undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Moloney, Mick: Reviews (Folder 1), 1971-1984 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Moloney, Mick: Reviews (Folder 2), 1985-2002 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Moloney, Mick: Reviews (Folder 3), undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Moloney, Mick: Yearly Planners, 1978, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Moloney, Mick: Yearly Planners, 1984-1985 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Moloney, Mick: Yearly Planners, 1986-1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Moloney, Mick: Yearly Planners, 1990-1992 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Moloney, Mick: Yearly Planners, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Moloney, Mick: Yearly Planners (Oversized), 2000 (Box Shared Tamiment 065, Folder 9)
  - Mick Moloney, Robbie O'Connell and Jimmy Keane, 1985-1990 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Molsky, Bruce, 2000 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Montez, Lola, circa 1994 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Mulhaire, Martin, 1981 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Mulvihill, Gail, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Mulvihill, Martin, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Mulvihill, Martin, 1987-1988 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Murphy, Danny, 1978 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Murphy, Delia, 1953-1982 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Murphy, Jim, undated (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Neary, Eleanor Kane, undated, 1980-1984 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - Nolan, Neil, undated (Box 18, Folder 35)
  - Noonan, Paddy, 1993-1994 (Box 18, Folder 36)
  - Nugent, Larry, circa 1995 (Box 18, Folder 37)
  - O'Brien, Paddy (Offaly), undated (Box 18, Folder 38)
  - O'Brien, Paddy (Tipperary), 1991 (Box 18, Folder 39)
  - O'Byrne DeWitt, undated (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Ochs, Bill, 1974-1983 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - O'Connell, Robbie, circa 1991 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - O'Donnell, Eugene, circa 1982-1994 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - O'Driscoll, Treasa, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - O'Grady, John and Lou, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - O'Grady, Mary, undated (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - O'Malley, Myles, 1951-1985 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - O'Neill, Francis (Folder 1), 1806-1999 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - O'Neill, Francis (Folder 2), 1806-1999 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - O'Sullivan, Jerry, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Patterson, Frank, 1993-1995 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Purcell, Al, undated (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Quinn, Carmel, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Quinn, Eamon, undated (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Reavy, Ed: Correspondence, 1977-1995 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Reavy, Ed: General (Folder 1), 1979-1995 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Reavy, Ed: General (Folder 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Reavy, Ed: Interviews, undated (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Reavy Jr., Ed, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Reavy, Joe, circa 1985 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Regan, Will, 1950-1991 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Reynolds, Paddy, 1983 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Ridge, John, undated (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Rooney, Pat, 1879-1940 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Russell, Micho, 1976-1994 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Simos, Mark, 1978, 1990 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Sands Family, 1988-1993 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Seeger, Mike, circa 1982 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Shea, Dick, 1979-1981 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Sheridan, Philip R.: MacGillicuddy, King of the Leprechauns, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Shute, Bill and Lisa Null, undated (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Sky, Pat, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Solas, 1996 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Standeven, Tom, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Stoner, Michael, 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Swan, Doc, undated (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Sunrush, 1999 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Sweeney's Men, 1969 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Teahan, Terry "Cuz", 1980-1982 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Thompson, Sue, 1979 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Thornton, Frank, 1978 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Touhey, Patsy, undated (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Trimble, Gerald, circa 1980 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Tunney, Paddy (Folder 1), 1976-1980 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Tunney, Paddy (Folder 2), 1980 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Van Kleeck, Dick, 1983-1984 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Vaulet, Phillippe, undated (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Vesey, John (Folder 1), undated (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Vesey, John (Folder 2), undated (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Ward, Brendan, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Weissman, Elaine, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Williams, John, 1992 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Williams, Sean, undated (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Winch, Terence Patrick, 1978-2000 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Yarrow, Peter, 2008 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Zahm, Charlie, 1992-1993 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Kovalcheck, Prof. Kas - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Gormley, Dennis, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 59)
- Series III: Academic, 1889-2011; 3 boxes
  Series III: Academic, 1889-2011 consists of research and teaching materials accrued by Dr. Moloney while acquiring his PhD from the University of Pennsylvania and during his teaching assignments at Villanova University, New York University, Georgetown University, Boston College. Materials include syllabi, lectures notes, reading lists, correspondence, and handwritten research notes. Also included are photocopied scholarly journal articles and student papers of various folklore and ethnicity topics.
  - American Conference for Irish Studies (ACIS): General (Folder 1), 1977-1979 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - American Conference for Irish Studies (ACIS): General (Folder 2), 1980-1993 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - American Conference for Irish Studies (ACIS): General (Folder 3), 1994-2001 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - American Conference for Irish Studies (ACIS): Papers, 1978-1991 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1936-1965 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1966-1972 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1973-1979 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1980 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1983-1989 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1989-1994 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity, undated (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Arts and Crafts, 1978-1991 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Dance (Folder 1), undated (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Dance (Folder 2), undated (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Irish and Irish-American (Folder 1), 1925-1973 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Irish and Irish-American (Folder 2), 1979-1987 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Irish and Irish-American (Folder 3), 1990-1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Irish and Irish-American (Folder 4), undated (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Articles: Folklore and Ethnicity- Music, 1955-1994 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Articles: Irish Music, 1976-1999 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Articles: Irish Music, undated (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Articles: Minstrelsy, undated (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Articles: Theater, 1889-1993 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Articles: Vaudeville, 1924-1961 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Articles: Vaudeville, 1982-2011 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Bibliographies and Reading Lists, 1981-1993 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Boston College, 1997-2000 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Conferences: Crossroads, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Conferences: Ethnic Readings in America: A Neglected Heritage, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Conferences: General, 1992-1999 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Conferences: Middle Atlantic Chapter of the Society for Ethnomusicology (MACSEM), 1991-1992 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Conferences: Presenting the Folk Arts, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Conferences: Re-Imagining Ireland- Correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Conferences: Re-Imagining Ireland- General, 2002 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence: Academic (Folder 1), 1975-1979 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Academic (Folder 2), 1980-1999 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Academic (Folder 3), undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Course Materials: Folklore and American Ethnic Groups, 1992-1996 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Course Materials: Folklore and Ethnicity (Folder 1), 1975-1980 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Course Materials: Folklore and Ethnicity (Folder 2), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Course Materials: Folklore of American Ethnic Groups, 1975-1993 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Course Materials: Folklore of Immigrant Groups (Folder 1), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Course Materials: Folklore of Immigrant Groups (Folder 2), 1975 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Course Materials: Irish-American Folk and Popular Culture, 1980-1981 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Course Materials: Irish and Irish-American Folklore (Folder 1), 1996 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Course Materials: Irish and Irish-American Folklore (Folder 2), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Course Materials: Irish and Irish-American Folklore and Popular Culture, undated (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Course Materials: Irish and Irish-American Folk Music, undated (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Course Materials: Irish Verbal Art, 1991 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Course Materials: New York University, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Course Materials: University of Pennsylvania- Folklore of Immigrant Groups, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Course Materials: University of Pennsylvania- Irish Folk Music and Society, undated (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Curricula: Athbheochan na Gaeilge (Restoration of the Irish Language), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Curricula: Celtic Culture: Four Winds, circa 1997 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Curricula: Famine, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Curricula: Famine- Oxfam, circa 1992 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Dissertation: Notes and Drafts, undated (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Dissertation: Research Materials, undated (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Bars, undated (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Dance Halls, undated (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Discs, undated (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Ethnicity, undated (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Ideology and Meaning, undated (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Irish Record Companies, undated (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Learning, undated (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Non-Irish, undated (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Production, undated (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Revival Movements, undated (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Sessions, undated (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Status of Musicians, undated (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Step Dance, undated (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Style and Variation/Aesthetics, undated (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Women, undated (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Dissertation: Research Notes- Young Irish-Americans, undated (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Georgetown, 1980-1994 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - George Washington University, 1980-1982 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Lecture: 1798, 1995 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Lecture: Banjo in Irish Music, undated (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Lecture: Celtic Music (delivered in Staten Island), undated (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Lecture: Irish-American Archives, undated (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Lecture: Irish Folklore (to Smithsonian Institution), 1995 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Lecture: Irish Immigration ("for Friedman's Class"), undated (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Lecture: Irish Music in America, undated (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Lecture: Irish Music on the American Stage, undated (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Lecture: Irish Rebel Songs (Class Presentation), undated (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Lecture: Irish Songs of the Civil War, undated (Box 22, Folder 10)
  - Lecture: Revivals (delivered in Rhode Island), undated (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - Lecture: Songs About 1916, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 12)
  - Lecture: Songs of Internationalism, Nationalism and Orangeism 1798-1998 (Box 22, Folder 13)
  - Lecture: Songs of Irish Immigration and Settlement, 1994 (Box 22, Folder 14)
  - Recommendation Letters, 1977-1994 (Box 22, Folder 15)
  - Research Materials: Ethnic Folklore and Culture, 1987-1994 (Box 22, Folder 16)
  - Research Notes: Protest Songs, undated (Box 22, Folder 17)
  - Student Papers: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1980-1981 (Box 22, Folder 18)
  - Student Papers: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 19)
  - Student Papers: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 20)
  - Student Papers: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1992 (Box 22, Folder 21)
  - Student Papers: Folklore and Ethnicity, 1992-1993 (Box 22, Folder 22)
  - Student Papers: Folklore and Ethnicity, undated (Box 22, Folder 23)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 24)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 25)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 26)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1983-1984 (Box 22, Folder 27)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 28)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 29)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 30)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1991 (Box 22, Folder 31)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, 1993 (Box 22, Folder 32)
  - Student Papers: Irish-American Culture, undated (Box 22, Folder 33)
  - Student Papers: New York University, 1980, undated (Box 22, Folder 34)
  - Student Papers: Villanova University, 1989 (Box 22, Folder 35)
  - University of Pennsylvania: Catalogs, 1990-1993 (Box 22, Folder 36)
  - University of Pennsylvania: Center for Irish Studies, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 37)